Stefanos

Kapsoritakis



Contact

Address:

Yo-Kylä 25A 26, Turku, Finland

Phone:

+358 44 230 320 7

Email:

stefan7@hotmail.gr

Links

LinkedIn	Portfolio	GitHub
in	S. K.	0

Languages

English - C2

Finnish - C1

Greek – C1

German - B1

Hobbies

- Working out
- Basketball
- Video Games

Summary

I'm a game design graduate specializing in Unity and C#. I am passionate about programming and improving my skills, Some of my hobbies include playing basketball and playing video games, I fell in love with them at a young age and decided to enter the business.

Skill Highlights

- C#
- WordPress
- GitHub, BitBucket
- Unity
- JavaScript
- React

Experience

Game Developer - 04/2021 - 06/2022

TurkuGameLab, Turku

- Commissioned Thesis
- Created a VR game in Unity that utilized hand-tracking and controllers
- Technologies used: Unity, C#, GitHub, Oculus Quest

Game Developer - 06/2020 – 07/2020

TurkuGameLab, Turku

- Practical Training
 - Collaborated in a team on a VR game
 - Technologies used: C#, Unity, BitBucket, HTC Vive

Web Developer – 03/2019 – 07/2019

Central-Paku Oy, Turku

- Practical Training
- Created the front-end webpage on a car rental company
- Technologies used: WordPress

Education

Bachelor of Engineering: Information and Communications

Technology – 2017-2022

Turku University of Applied Sciences, FI

Certifications

English Competency Certificate, The University of Michigan Certificate of Competency in English

German Competency Certificate, Göethe Institute B1

Bachelor's Thesis:

https://www.theseus.fi/handle/10024/754933